Hello Hello Friends My name is Rahul
Welcome to our YouTube channel
today we are going to talk about Tata AIG
Medical Treatment Plant Friends if
you watch this video you will get
complete information about this plant so that you can subscribe
for yourself If you subscribe the
appointed subscribe
comes under the extra family floater plan
so here we will talk about all the types of plans
its terms
and conditions in this plan so the
terms and conditions are mentioned that if any person
wants to subscribe maximum entry then
we will subscribe here subscribe you will
get coverage of a seven member only
Next we will talk now if any school owner does
not subscribe then
subscribe here on top of that that means he will
subscribe to it if you are
watching this if you
definitely subscribe to normal here if you
subscribe and they have
because if the company
presented a misguided mixture then the company
can dismiss you tomorrow or cancel the policy
and if you do not even follow the time given by them then
its  Meaning that you must
first subscribe so that the
youth can subscribe that
war, it means school appointment, so we are given
30 days extra time for a problem
that we simply because it is
getting time every day, that is to
appoint the policy, if you subscribe, then
always like if you
subscribe to any company, village only at the
time of subjects
here setting airlines, that is if you want to
increase your time, okay, from 5 lakhs,
if you feel that you have taken
15, then that is
possible only on time, which is of the company, that you
subscribe to the subscription and if you
subscribe to my channel, withdrawal
Rinku phase, it means appointment, withdrawal subscription, that the
liquid arising from this, then
you must subscribe, now school subscription, so
when you want to take the benefit of the policy, it means that it is
mandatory to be admitted in the hospital for 24 hours, only then we
get the benefit of the claim money here,
secondly, let us talk about this and suppose if you have
taken the policy  It goes and when it comes
to tractor then subscribe that is why
I have to subscribe subscribe subscribe
subscribe to the channel
quads are not available or the patient is
in a condition that he needs to be taken from home
to hospital then in that condition
you can subscribe to any channel from the hospital doctor of the company, that is
here you
must subscribe to one thing subscribe so
here we start maximum Veer Varsha for Ghaghra and family and
subscribe member to
come to your page from particular play
which you can take later so you will have to incur expenses so we will
talk about nourishing the
liquid and subscribe so if
you subscribe for yourself subscribe
and subscribe then you subscribe
village subscribe that war so
subscribe there are
trees like boss we
consulted a doctor there may be some consultancy or took
medicines so there may be expenses for that
reports etc. then you can keep those as well you can do
small subscriptions which
I have already subscribed that is skin so that
he can take benefit here
okay so here Sangh
subscribe
Samsung Health  Checkup benefit will be given here
and after this, like here you don't need to
subscribe to this channel for a moment, that
means
[music] the
entire money of score treatment, subscribe
to our channel,
which method, if I had taken a policy of 10 lakhs, then
next year my voice will be kept at 15, if
I have taken it, if I have taken the appointment,
subscribe to the channel, definitely subscribe, so subscribe
here, subscribe,
more than the money means 80, subscribe to the whole India,
now about the school, now let
us talk about the
benefits from this, okay, now we will talk about that
subscribe, that means subscribe,
subscribe to my channel, subscribe, in
every company under the appointment quality,
here you will get one, there is a 2 year
guaranteed for the month and this is some
limit, all the subscribers, subscribe, if there is a
problem, if there is a problem, then
subscribe, if you subscribe,
subscribe, free subscribe,
if suppose today I took a policy and
I already had some disease, okay, that
disease, here I have a guarantee of two years
in some company, do not
forget to subscribe, subscribe, so if any
I'll tell you soon that you can
subscribe to this, medical and health
benefits, but this is a
space where companies never cover certain things,
which is very important for us to know. For example, if
we talk about
any company and subscribe to the channel,
if someone subscribes and
subscribes to the channel, if they
like music, let
's say they are handicapped or have some other
problem, then the company does
n't cover these things. Okay,
you should keep this in mind while taking this thing.
Subscribe, and if you are mentally challenged, subscribe
and subscribe to the channel. If you haven't subscribed to the
channel, you're
not doing Gabbar. If you
try to attempt suicide, okay, that
means companies do all these things,
ask, comment, share, subscribe, loot,
and don't subscribe. So here
I've told you that you can
also subscribe to this war benefits,
like you keep getting such appointments on
this, so thank you so much, please
subscribe to this and don't
forget to press the bell icon. Thank you.